Lisa Montin

Gösvägen 46 Cell: 0768 521 521 181 30 Lidingö lisa_jugas@hotmail.com

Overview

Customer-service focused with 4 seasons experience working as winter sports instructor at different locations including Norway and Canada. Excellent ability to work independently or as part of a team; multicultural awareness with a high level of adaptability. Responsible, encouraging, playful, including, organized and prepared.

Professional Experience

Lidingö särskola

Mars 2012, October 2012 - February 2013

Student assistant

Bodal, Lidingö

Give support and help young students with learning difficulties and disabilities.

Geilo Fjellandsby

December 2008 to April 2009

Ski, Snowboard and Cross country instructor

Geilo, Norway

Welcome guests to the ski resort and offer private instruction in alpine and cross-country skiing and snowboarding, all levels. Plan and perform the complimentary children's activities. Arrange activities for visiting conference guests.

Marmot Basin

November 2007 to April 2008

Ski instructor

Marmot Basin, Jasper, Canada

Teach guests to ski or improve their technique and guide guests on skis on the mountain. All levels, all ages, groups and privates. Assist in competitions and assist in general ski-instructor improvement.

Geilolia Ski school

December 2006 to April 2007

Ski, Snowboard and Cross country instructor

Geilo, Norway

Instruct in ski snowboard and cross country, group and private, all levels. Arrange activities for conference guests as well as children's activities.

Geilolia Ski school

December 2005 to April 2006

Ski, Snowboard and Cross country instructor

Geilo, Norway

Instruct in ski snowboard and cross country, group and private, all levels. Arrange activities for conference guests as well as children's activities.

Education

EC Utbildning Augusti 2019 - Ongoing

Frontend Development

Certificate

Solna, Stockholm, Sweden

2-year vocational education

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, UX/UI, mssql, react, angular, nodeJS, T-SQL

InfoKomp vuxenutbildning

Augusti 2018 - October 2018

Programmering 1

Course

Distans Kista

• C++

De Anza College

September 2009 - December 2011

Health Technologies

Certificate

Cupertino, CA, USA

Medical secretary

Swedish College of Travel and Tourism

August 2004 - December 2005

Travel, tourism and ski instructing

Certificate

Orsa, Dalarna, Sweden

Post-secondary training program

• Tourism and ski instructing certification

Tannbergsskolan

August 1999- June 2002

Civics/Economy

Certificate

Lycksele, Sweden

3-Year Upper Secondary School

• Civics economy program with a tailormade schedule for training and competing in cross country skiing.

Other Experience

Privately invested in, renovated and sold houses in Santa Barbara, CA. Mars 2013 - August 2014.

Stay-at-Home Mom to three lovely boys August 2014 - August 2019.

Ongoing activities at Udemy:

- Learn and understand NodeJS w. Anthony Alicea,
- The Complete 2020 Web Development Bootcamp w. Dr Angela Yu,
- Javascript: Understanding the Weird Parts w. Anthony Alicea.